adriagate.com 2019-12-15

# Privacy policy

**1\. INTRODUCTION**

Adriagate Travel Agency d.o.o. (hereinafter: the Agency) recognizes and appreciates your right to data confidentiality and commits itself to preserving security of data collected through the website https://www.adriagate.com

The Agency collects, processes and stores your personal data in accordance with the EU's General Data Protection Act (GDPR) and other applicable regulations. The data will not be forwarded to third parties or brought to third countries, with the exception of situations where it acts as a prerequisite for the fulfilment of contracted services (eg accommodation, airline, carrier, insurance).

We will consider that the continued use of  https://www.adriagate.com  represents your acceptance of terms listed bellow.

 **2\. USE OF PERSONAL DATA  **

Your personal data is collected and used only on the basis of data that you have voluntarily given to the Agency, either by way of registration (personal data such as: name, country, address, city, e-mail, date or simply the year of birth) or using our website https://www.adriagate.com 

Collected personal data is stored in electronic form and all appropriate technical and organizational measures are applied to prevent personal data breach. Received e-mails with your personal information will only be used by the Agency for the purpose of completing your requests.

 **3.RESERVATION**

When booking accommodation, travel or other services offered by the Agency, personal information of the reservation holder, who must be of age will be required (eg name, address, contact telephone and e-mail address) as well as data regarding other service users (eg name, date of birth) . Only the data necessary for the execution of the service will be available exclusively to the partners taking part in the service execution (accommodation, transportation, insurance and travel companion).

Payment information (e.g., bank card number, expiration date) is particularly protected and will only be available to banks or credit card companies with the purpose of payment authorisation. Please note that the registration at https://www.adriagate.com  is only possible for adults of 18 years of age and older. When registering at https://www.adriagate.com  the user chooses the password independently and in accordance with this is held responsible for its protection and prevention of abuse by third parties.

 **4\. COOKIES**

Cookies allow the Agency to collect statistical data with relation to user behavior at https://www.adriagate.com  (for example, on which parts of the site the user spends the longest or the shortest amount of time), which Internet browser  (e.g. Internet Explorer, Opera, Safari, Google Chrome,Firefox) is used and similar.

Cookies are a small set of data sent from the https://www.adriagate.com/  server to the user's computer, and serves as an anonymous identifier. Cookies are also used to facilitate navigation through web pages (for example, you do not need to enter registration data each time). Cookies are not used to access user data or to track user activity after leaving https://www.adriagate.com. 

The agency reserves the right to use cookies at https://www.adriagate.com but each user may prohibit receiving cookies by editing / changing the settings in their Internet browser.

 **5\. CONNECTIONS**

https://www.adriagate.com contains links to other websites that are not owned by the Agency. Accordingly, we warn and ask the users take into consideration the fact that the Agency can not be held responsible for matters regarding privacy protection on the stated internet websites. Therefore, users are encouraged to read the Privacy Statement of each web site they access.

 **6\. DIGITAL MARKETING**

Contact information, such as your name and e-mail address, is necessary when you want to use the services of receiving promotional materials from the Agency. Promotional materials include information about service, special offers and newsletter.

The service can be disabled at any time by activating the "Logout" link at the end of an email or by sending a delete request from the digital marketing list at info@adriagate.com 

 **7\. SAFETY**

The Agency undertakes all security measures to ensure data protection, during input, transfer, data processing, and storage. Data access is limited and the only employees in possession of it are those who require it in order to perform business activities.

The personal data transferred to the Agency upon registration shall be kept during the existence of the website or during the registration of the user. Any information provided to the Agency upon registration on the Internet site will be destroyed at the latest when shutting it down or until the user requests otherwise.

Users have the right to ask for information about their personal data being processed by the Agency as well as  modify or delete them at any time by sending a request to hrm@adriagate.com 

 **8\. NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES**

In case of changes related to the privacy rules, the notice will be posted on the cover page of the website with the aim of informing the user.

Adriagate Travel Agency d.o.o. 

Vukovarska 156, 21000 Split

Croatia

e: hrm@adriagate.com

t: +38521 271 870

Split, May 23th, 2018
